paypoint.co.uk 2016-09-13

# PayPoint — Privacy & Cookies

PayPoint may collect certain information about you in the course of your use of this website and in the course of correspondence with you. PayPoint takes privacy and security of your information seriously and will only use such personal information as set out in this privacy policy. By using this website and submitting your information to us you agree to us using your personal information in accordance with this policy.

This section of our website also tells you what cookies we use on different parts of the site and how to reject or delete those cookies. PayPoint does not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you.

## Privacy Policy

**What information will we collect about you?**

PayPoint will collect the information that you submit to us using the contact details on this website and any other applications that may exist on this website. PayPoint will also collect data about your use of this website.

How will PayPoint use the information it collects about you?

PayPoint may do the following with your personal information:

  * > record and monitor your use of this website for internal purposes which may include analysis of usage, measurement of website performance and generation of marketing reports;
  * > use it for the purposes of investor relations to market our products and services to you in the future and this may involve contacting you using the contact details you give us; and
  * > transfer it to our international offices and branches and/or allow the information to be accessed by personnel outside the EEA as well as within it (you should be aware that in territories outside the EEA laws and practices relating to the protection of personal data are likely to be different and in some cases may be weaker than those within the EEA).

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties except as detailed above or where a government, regulatory body or the law requires or allows us to disclose your personal information.

**Updating and accessing your information**

If you wish to update or amend the information which PayPoint may hold about you or wish PayPoint to cease using your data please contact us [enquiries@paypoint.com](mailto:enquiries@paypoint.com). Alternatively you may write to us at: 1 The Boulevard, Shire Park, Welwyn Garden City, Herts AL7 1EL.

You have a right under the Data Protection Act 1998 (and if you live in the Republic of Ireland, under its equivalent data protection legislation) to access the information PayPoint holds about you, subject to certain conditions. If you wish to make an application to access this information please contact us [enquiries@paypoint.com](mailto:enquiries@paypoint.com). Alternatively you may write to us at: PayPoint, 1 The Boulevard, Shire Park, Welwyn Garden City, Herts AL7 1EL.

These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with English law and the parties hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts in respect of all matters arising in connection herewith.

PayPoint has not reviewed, is not responsible for, and accepts no liability in respect of, any information or opinion contained on any other website.

If you wish to purchase services from us you must abide by our Terms and Conditions of use applicable to the relevant service.

## Cookie Policy

**Just browsing**

If you are just looking around our website we use analytical or performance cookies. These help us understand our visitors interaction with our website which enables us to improve the way our website works, for example, making it easy for users to find the information they need. These cookies do not collect information that identifies you. All information collected is aggregated and therefore anonymous. They are only used to improve the performance of our website

If you do not want this to take place you can adjust your browser settings or visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which tells you how to do this on a variety of browsers. Only use our site if you consent to the cookies being installed. Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of the site.

**Contact**

You will not be contacted by us if you just look around the site. We will only contact you if you complete a call back or contact request.

The rest of this section gives you a list of what performance cookies are set by our website and a description of how they are used.

**Domain** | **Cookie Name** | **Cookie Usage**  
---|---|---  
PayPoint | _utma | This Google Analytics cookie is used to determine the number of unique visitors to our website and it is updated with each page viewed. This cookie persists for 2 years unless deleted by the user.  
PayPoint | _utmb | This Google Analytics cookie is used to establish and continue a user session with this site, this cookie is updated to expire in 30 minutes, thus continuing a single session for as long as user activity continues within 30-minute intervals.  
PayPoint | _utmc | This Google Analytics cookie is a tracking code to determine session status. Persists for the duration of the browser session unless deleted  
PayPoint | _utmz | 

This Google Analytics cookie stores the type of referral used by the visitor to reach your site. Persists for six months unless deleted.  
  
PayPoint | _utmv | 

Google Analytics Cookie. Used for user-custom variables in Analytics
